{
    "id": "e2b3013e07044a41903fa91193ce35ca",
    "title": "Find the mistakes",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7fa13281b62142cd84692ad0093027b7",
            "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I suggested .......................... home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "her to go",
                        "that she should go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We don’t allow people .................................... in the kitchen.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to smoke",
                        "smoking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I didn’t ask him to .................................... the meal.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "pay",
                        "pay for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I hate the thought .................................. old.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to get",
                        "of getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The cleaning is ................................. by midday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to finish",
                        "to be finished"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She lets her children .................................... up very late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stay",
                        "to stay"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We arrive ............................... New York on Tuesday morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "These sheets are .................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to wash",
                        "to be washed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The doctor suggested .................................... a long holiday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to take",
                        "taking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you finished .................................... the car?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to mend",
                        "mending"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}